A Guide to the Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976, RG 3 FA094
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976, RG 3
Rockefeller Archive Center
Rockefeller, John D., III (John Davison), 1906-1978
Rockefeller, David
Rockefeller, Laurance Spelman
Mauze, Abby Rockefeller
Rockefeller, Nelson A. (Nelson Aldrich)
FA094
635.62 Cubic Feet 1656 containers.
Conditions Governing Access note
Open for research in accordance with the terms of donation from the David Rockefeller Estate, January 2019. Brittle or damaged items are available at the discretion of RAC.
Researchers interested in accessing audiovisual material (audio cassettes, VHS, etc.) in this collection must use an access surrogate. The original items may not be accessed because of preservation concerns. To request an access surrogate be made, or if you are unsure if there is an access surrogate, please contact an archivist.
When requesting to view audiovisual material, please refer to the Title and the AV Number (example: AV 1916). Researchers are asked to check the "Restrictions" note for each Title. If a Title does not currently have an access copy, please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
Arrangement
Original order. Alphabetical, primarily by subject/topic.
Biographical / Historical
The central figure in the creation and operation of the Standard Oil Company during its rise to the top of the petroleum industry, John D. Rockefeller (JDR) established for the family a leading role in business and philanthropy. From the days of his earliest employment, Rockefeller, a devout Baptist, was generous in his giving to worthy causes, especially those of a religious nature. During the 1890s he developed an orderly system of philanthropic giving through an office staff that included his close advisor, Frederick T. Gates (1853-1929) and his son, John D. Rockefeller, Jr. (1874-1960). With the advise of these and other associates, Rockefeller established the University of Chicago, The Rockefeller Institute for Medical Research (now The Rockefeller University), the Rockefeller Foundation, and other philanthropic organizations working nationally and internationally in the fields of education, religion, and health. Rockefeller's total donations to philanthropic endeavors are estimated to have been $540 million.
John D. Rockefeller, Jr. (JDR Jr.) joined his father's office on October 1, 1897. He oversaw the expansion and diversification of the philanthropic work begun by his father. During his lifetime, the younger Rockefeller gave more than $537 million to educational, religious, cultural, medical, and other charitable projects.
John D. Rockefeller, Jr. and his wife, Abby Aldrich Rockefeller (1874-1948), passed the Rockefeller philanthropic impulse on to their children. John D. 3rd (1906-1978), Nelson A. (1908-1979), Laurance S. (1910-2004), Winthrop (1912-1973), and David (1915-2017) further expanded and diversified Rockefeller influence and interests, establishing their own philanthropic organizations, most notably the Rockefeller Brothers Fund (1940), and becoming more active politically.
In the period following the Second World War, John D. Rockefeller, Jr.'s sons returned from service to assume an increasing role in family business and philanthropic endeavors, even as they were pursuing their own careers and interests. The office provided family members with a range of services from routine office support (office space, staffing, purchasing, payroll and accounting, travel, security) to specialized investment, economic and philanthropic advising, legal counsel, a library collection, and a public relations staff.
To support their broad activity – a 1951 list of the family's associations detailed more than seventy organizations in which the five Rockefeller brothers actively participated in a business or philanthropic capacity – the family had long relied on a system of associates who worked with individual family members and provided specialized assistance and advice. The Rockefeller family office was originally located at 26 Broadway in the Standard Oil Building, but it moved to Rockefeller Center when the RCA Building opened in the fall of 1933. The family office occupied the 56th floor (and eventually the 54th and 55th floors) of the RCA Building, and was often known as Room 5600. Rockefeller philanthropies such as the American Conservation Association, the Rockefeller Brothers Fund and the Sealantic Fund also operated out of the family office space, and many affiliated businesses (such as Eastern Air Lines and Rockresorts, Inc.) were neighboring Rockefeller Center tenants.
Scope and Contents
The 1962-1976 general files chronicle management of the philanthropic affairs of the third generation of the Rockefeller family primarily Abby Rockefeller Mauze, John D. Rockefeller 3rd, Nelson A. Rockefeller, Laurance S. Rockefeller, Winthrop Rockefeller, and David Rockefeller.
Over the years the Rockefeller family has been involved in virtually all aspects of modern philanthropy at the local, national and international levels through their foundation activities as well as their individual personal giving. Major interests include: physical and mental health, conservation, education, international relations, politics, population, religion, social welfare, the visual and performing arts, cultural exchange programs, and economic and social development of underdeveloped areas.
The general files primarily consist of correspondence, reports, pamphlets, memoranda, charters and certificates of incorporation, minutes and meeting records as well as documentation of contributions, finance and investment materials, real estate, newspaper clippings, diaries, notebooks, calendars, audio tapes, and printed material.
Related Materials
FA1502 Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1996, Index Cards, RG 3-RG 44.
Westchester County (N.Y.); Agriculture; Charities -- Investments; Education; Economics; Philanthropy -- New York (State); Political science; Philanthropy -- United States; Philanthropy; Philanthropy -- New York (N.Y.); Charities; Charitable contributions; Charitable uses, trusts, and foundations; Richford (N.Y.); Race and society; Environmental sciences; Photographs; North Dakota; Race relations; Illinois; Arts; Cemeteries; Energy; International relations
- Rockefeller Family and Associates (Room 5600), General Files, 1962-1976; 3
  - A Miscellaneous - A-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
  - A Miscellaneous - Advertising Council, 1962-1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - A Miscellaneous - Aldrich, Winthrop W., 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - A Miscellaneous - Arnold, Stanley N., 1964-1970 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Agriculture - A-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 2, Folder 1-3)
  - Agriculture - Center for Rural Studies, 1972-1974 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Agriculture - Foreign - International Institute for Rural Reconstruction, 1962-1973 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Agriculture - National Farm Workers Service Center, Inc., 1962-1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Agriculture - National Farm Workers Service Center, Inc. - Contributions (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Agriculture - New Communities, Inc., 1969-1974 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - American International Association for Economic and Social Development (AIA) - A-I, 1962-1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - American International Association for Economic and Social Development (AIA) - J-Z, 1962-1974 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - American International Association for Economic and Social Development (AIA) - Articles (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - American International Association for Economic and Social Development (AIA) - Contributions (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
  - American International Association for Economic and Social Development (AIA) - IRI Research Institute (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - American International Association for Economic and Social Development (AIA) - IRI Research Institute - Articles (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Applicants - A-C, 1962-1976 (Box 5, Folder 1-4)
  - Applicants - D-H, 1962-1976 (Box 6, Folder 1-4)
  - Applicants - I-M, 1962-1976 (Box 7, Folder 1-3)
  - Applicants - N-S, 1962-1976 (Box 8, Folder 1-4)
  - Applicants - T-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 9, Folder 1-2)
  - Arts - A-Am, 1962-1976 (Box 9, Folder 3-4)
  - Arts - An-Cn, 1962-1976 (Box 10, Folder 1-4)
  - Arts - Co-H, 1962-1976 (Box 11, Folder 1-3)
  - Arts - I-L, 1962-1976 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
  - Arts - M-Na, 1962-1976 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
  - Arts - Nb-P, 1962-1976 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
  - Arts - L. Outhwaite - Study of Cultural Institutions and Government (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Arts - L. Outhwaite - Study of Cultural Institutions and Government (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Arts - L. Outhwaite - Study of Cultural Institutions and Government - Europe (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Arts - L. Outhwaite - Museums and the Future (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Q-R, 1962-1976 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Arts - S-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
  - Arts - American Crafts Council - Shaker Film, 1969-1973 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Arts - American Crafts Council, 1964-1976 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Arts - American Friends of Canada, 1972-1976 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Arts - American Institute of Architects, 1972-1976 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Arkansas Art Center, 1962-1975 (Box 18, Folder 1-2)
  - Arts - Arkansas Art Center - Public Affairs - Clurman, 1962 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Arkansas Art Center - Contributions, 1962-1965 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Arts - Arkansas Art Center - Fund Raising, 1962-1963 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Arts - Arts Councils of America, 1965-1966 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Associated Councils of the Arts - Advocates for the Arts, 1972-1976 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Arts - Associated Councils of the Arts - General - A-Z (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Associated Councils of the Arts - Partnership for the Arts, 1971-1973 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Associated Councils of the Arts - Contributions, 1972-1975 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Arts - Associated Councils of the Arts - Printed Material, 1967-1976 (Box 20, Folder 3-4)
  - Arts - Business Committee for the Arts - General, 1972-1976 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Business Committee for the Arts - A-Z, 1967-1976 (Box 21, Folder 2-3)
  - Arts - Business Committee for the Arts - Aspen Conference, 1967 May (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Arts - Business Committee for the Arts - Clippings, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Business Committee for the Arts - Contributions, 1967-1968 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Arts - Business Committee for the Arts - Finances, 1970-1971 (Box 22, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Business Committee for the Arts - Meetings/Minutes, 1966-1976 (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Arts - Business Committee for the Arts - Printed Material, 1967-1972 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - Arts - Business Committee for the Arts - Members, 1967 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Business Committee for the Arts - Reports, 1968-1971 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Arts - Center for the Arts at Ithaca, 1967-1971 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Century Association - A-L, 1962-1976 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Arts - Century Association, 1962-1976 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Children's Art Carnival, 1975-1976 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Arts - Committee to Rescue Italian Art, 1967 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Conference on Arts and Young People, 1966 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Arts - Island Center of St. Croix, Ltd., 1966-1971 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Council for the Arts in Westchester, 1973-1976 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Arts - Cultural League of New York, 1967-1970 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Inter-American Foundation for the Arts, 1964-1971 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Arts - International Association of Plastic Arts, 1962-1964 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Arts - Jackson Hole Fine Arts Foundation, 1962-1966 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Arts - John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, 1967-1976 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - General - A-H, 1956-1976 (Box 26, Folder 2-3)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - General - I-R, 1956-1976 (Box 27, Folder 1-3)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Aims and Purpose, 1963-1971 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - General - S-Z, 1956-1976 (Box 28, Folder 2-3)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Annual Report, 1959-1972 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Applicants, 1963-1968 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Appreciation, 1964-1970 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Articles, 1967-1968 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Building Costs, 1958-1966 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Printed Matter (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Board of Directors, 1967-1971 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Board of Directors, 1956-1966 (Box 30, Folder 1-2)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - By-laws, 1956-1976 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Clippings, 1962-1969 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Constituent Relations, 1967-1970 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Miscellaneous) - A-Z, 1958-1972 (Box 31, Folder 1-4)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Federation of Economic Organizations, 1958-1972 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Mrs. Vincent Astor, 1958-1972 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Mr. & Mrs. John F. Bryce, 1958-1972 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Vivian B. Allen Foundation, Inc., 1958-1972 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Confidential, 1958-1972 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Corporate Giving, 1958-1972 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Shelby Cullom Davis, 1958-1972 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - French Government, 1958-1972 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - John A. Hartford Foundation, Inc., 1958-1972 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Arthur A. Houghton, Jr., 1958-1972 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Albert A. List, 1958-1972 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Rockefeller Family Members, 1962-1967 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Mrs. C. Ruxton Love, Jr., 1958-1972 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Stavros S. Niarchos (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Colonel S. Vanderbilt (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Vanderbilt, Harold S., 1958-1972 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - Wien, Lawrence A., 1958-1972 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Contributions (Misc.) - John D. Rockefeller 3rd, 1958-1972 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Diary Notes, 1955-1959 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Employees, 1965-1970 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Employee Benefits Plan, 1962-1969 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Film Committee and Department, 1966-1971 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Film Society, 1972-1975 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Finances, 1963-1976 (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fund Raising, 1969-1976 (Box 36, Folder 3-4)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising, 1967-1968 (Box 37, Folder 1-2)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising, 1963-1966 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - Individuals - A-Z (Box 38, Folder 2-3)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - Committee for the Performing Arts at Lincoln Center, 1970 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - Corporate Support, 1967-1971 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - Colonel Henry Crown, 1954-1969 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - Mrs. Josephine H. Graeber, 1961-1969 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - John Paul Getty, 1960-1968 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - Juilliard (John D. Rockefeller 3rd Kit), 1968 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - Joseph Kennedy Memorial Foundation, 1960-1966 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - Labor, 1964-1969 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - Gustave L. Levy, 1964-1965 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - Development Committee Meetings/Minutes, 1964-1965 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Fundraising - Lincoln Center Fund Meetings/Minutes, 1965-1970 (Box 40, Folder 4-5)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Furnishings and Art Objects, 1966-1970 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Juilliard School of Music, 1964-1972 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Juilliard School of Music - Chamber Music Society, 1967-1976 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Land Acquisition, 1964-1968 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Legal, 1959-1964 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    Conditions Governing Access
    Restricted material - Legal matters.
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Library Museum, 1963-1972 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Library Museum - Toscanini Memorial Archive, 1964-1971 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Lincoln Center Student Program, 1966-1969 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Meetings/Minutes Board of Directors, 1956-1976 (Box 42, Folder 6-7, Box 43, Folder 1-5, Box 44, Folder 1-4, Box 45, Folder 1-2)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Meetings/Minutes Building Committee, 1957-1960 (Box 45, Folder 3-4, Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Meetings/Minutes Executive Committee, 1961-1971 (Box 46, Folder 2-3, Box 47, Folder 1-3)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Meetings/Minutes Lincoln Center Council, 1966-1971 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Memos, 1969-1971 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - New York City - Relationship, 1966-1969 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Metropolitan Opera, 1966-1973 (Box 48, Folder 1-2)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - New York City - Arts Council, 1965-1967 (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - New York Shakespeare Festival, 1973 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - New York State Theater, 1964-1971 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Philharmonic Hall, 1962-1970 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Policy Planning, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Printed Material, 1956-1976 (Box 49, Folder 2-4, Box 50, Folder 1-3, Box 51, Folder 1-2)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Releases, 1964-1971 (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - The Repertory Theater of L.C. (Vivian Beaumont Theater), 1964-1973 (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Arts - Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - William Schuman, 1961-1970 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Municipal Art Society of New York, 1964-1966 (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Arts - Mountain Artisans, 1970-1971 (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Arts - National Council on the Arts - National Endowment for the Arts, 1962-1976 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Arts - National Endowment for the Arts - Printed Matter (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Arts - New York State Council on the Arts (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Arts - Partnership for the Arts, 1970-1972 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Royal Society of the Arts, London, 1966-1968 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Arts - New York State Council on the Arts - Printed Material (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Arts - New York State Council on the Arts (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Arts - San Francisco Art Institute, 1966-1971 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Saratoga Performing Arts Center, Inc., 1962-1976 (Box 55, Folder 2-3, Box 56, Folder 1-2)
  - Arts - Saratoga Performing Arts Center - Clippings, 1963-1965 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Saratoga Performing Arts Center - Finances/Fund Raising, 1967-1971 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Arts - Saratoga Performing Arts Center - Fund Raising, 1963-1966 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Saratoga Performing Arts Center - Printed Material, 1964-1969 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Arts - Saratoga Performing Arts Center - Minutes/Meetings, 1967-1976 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Saratoga Performing Arts Center - Public Affairs, 1966 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Arts - Sunrise, Inc., 1965-1971 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Arts - Dance A-M, 1962-1976 (Box 58, Folder 1-2)
  - Arts - Dance - Ballet Theatre Foundation, Inc., 1962-1976 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Expeditions, 1962-1971 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Arts - Films A-Z, 1972-1976 (Box 59, Folder 1-4)
  - Arts - Films - United Productions, Inc., 1972-1973 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Arts - Dance N-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Furnishings, 1962-1969 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Arts - Galleries A-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 60, Folder 3, Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Libraries - A-K, 1962-1976 (Box 61, Folder 2-3)
  - Arts - Libraries - L-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Libraries - Center for the Study of the Presidency, 1967-1976 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Arts - Libraries - New York Public Library, 1967-1976 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Arts - Libraries - Pierpont Morgan Library, 1962-1976 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Libraries - Seal Harbor Library, 1962-1971 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Arts - Memorials A-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 63, Folder 3-4)
  - Arts - Museums - A-F, 1962-1976 (Box 64, Folder 1-3)
  - Arts - Museums - G-M, 1962-1976 (Box 65, Folder 1-4)
  - Arts - Museums - M-N, 1962-1976 (Box 66, Folder 1-3)
  - Arts - Museums - O-S, 1962-1976 (Box 67, Folder 1-4)
  - Arts - Museums - T-Z, 1962-1976 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Museums - Air Force Museum Foundation, Inc., 1962-1971 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Arts - Museums - American Museum in Britain, 1962-1976 (Box 68, Folder 3, Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Arts - Museums - American Association of Museums, 1962-1976 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Arts - Museums - American Museum of Immigration, 1962-1966 (Box 69, Folder 2)